Here, we have a variable called myName,
这是一个叫做 myName 的变量
which just points to a string, Andrew.
设为字符串“Andrew”.
This is variables in the Javascript file,
这是在该 Javascript 文件中的变量
but it is not inside any function,
但它不位于任何函数中
so it is global scope.
因此是全局作用域
Let us now go ahead and write a function called introduceMyself,
现在编写一个函数 叫做 introduceMyself
and define a local variable inside it.
并在其中定义一个局部变量
Great, So here we
这是
have the variable you, which points to a student.
设为 student 的 you 变量
And again this is a local variable,
它是局部变量
meaning that it's declared directly within introduceMyself.
表示它直接在 introduceMyself 中声明
Let's do one more thing and write a function called introduce,
我们再写一个函数 叫做 introduce
and return it from introduceMyself.
并从 introduceMyself 中返回它
Great.
好的
So where going to see what is going on here.
我们看看会发生什么情况
We have introduce which all it's going to do,
这是 introduce 函数
is that it is going to print out a message to the console,
它的作用是向控制台中输出一条消息
and that message references two variables that we have defined here.
该消息引用了我们在此处定义的两个变量
We have you, and we also have myName.
包括 you 和 myName
So let us break these both down and see what is happening.
分析下二者 看看发生了什么情况
We know that myName is a variable defined outside of this entire function,
我们知道 myName 是在整个函数之外定义的变量
meaning that it is a global variable with global scope,
表示它是具有全局作用域的全局变量
and it is available for all functions to use,
所有函数都可以使用它
including introduceMyself, and introduce.
包括 introduceMyself 和 introduce
So, that makes sense,
我们知道该函数了
but what about this variable over here?
但是这个 you 变量呢？
You. It might look kind of odd because you is referenced by this function introduce,
它看起来有点奇怪 因为 introduce 函数引用了 you
even though you, was never passed in as an argument,
虽然 you 从未作为参数传入其中
nor was you, ever declaring a local variable within introduce.
you 也没有在 introduce 中被声明为局部变量
This is all possible because a [inaudible] function scope includes
这一切都可行 因为嵌套函数作用域
variables declared in this scope where the function was defined in the first place.
包括在该作用域中定义的变量 函数一开始是在该作用域内定义的
So in other words, you is available,
换句话说 可以访问 you
because introduce still has access to its parent function scope,
因为 introduce 依然可以访问其父函数的作用域
and that is exactly where you is defined in the first place.
you 正是在该作用域内定义的
Finally, let's call introduceMyself and see the entire message.
最后 我们调用 introduceMyself 看看整个消息
And there you have it.
就是这个消息
Hello student, I'm Andrew.
Hello  student, I'm Andrew！